<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IndianMonuments</string>
    <string name="Redfortinfo">The Red Fort was the official seat of Mughal rule and authority from 1648 onwards, when the 5th Mughal emperor, Shah Jahan, decided to move the capital of the empire from Agra to Delhi. Constructed using red sandstone, it remains one of the architectural marvels of the Mughal era. It is one of the monuments in India which has been granted the status of a UNESCO World Heritage Site. It was awarded this distinction in 2007.</string>
    <string name="Tajmahalinfo">The Taj Mahal is one of the seven wonders of the world and is considered to be the most popular tourist attraction in the country in addition to being one of the most important historical monuments in India. A symbol of love, the Taj was built by Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan for his queen Mumtaz. Tagore described the Taj as an eardrop on the cheek of eternity. The monument attracts a lot of tourists all around the year.</string>
    <string name="Indiagateinfo">The All India War Memorial, popularly known as the India Gate, is a war memorial located in New Delhi. It is dedicated to the 82,000 soldiers, both Indian and British, who died during the First World War and the Third Anglo-Afghan War. The Amar Jawan Jyoti is the burning structure, right underneath the archway, which symbolizes the eternal, immortal soldiers of India.</string>
    <string name="Goldentempleinfo">Also called Sri Harmandir Sahib or Swarna Mandir (Golden Temple), the shrine was designed by Guru Arjan Sahib and its foundation laid by Muslim saint Hazrat Mian Mir ji of Lahore on 1st December 1588. Known to be one of the most important histotrical monuments in India, the temple attracts thoudands of devotees and pilgrims around the year from all over the world. </string>
    <string name="Lotustempleinfo">Commonly known as Lotus temple, this monument is one of the seven Baha"i Houses of Worship. The Lotus Temple is one of the most visited attractions in the city and is open to all, regardless of religion, or any other distinction. It is situated near mandir marg in Kalkaji, New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="Hawamahalinfo">The Hawa Mahal stands at the intersection of the main road in Jaipur, Badi Chaupad. It is regarded as the signature building of Jaipur and was built by Maharaja Sawai Pratap Singh. Considered as one of the most important and culturally rich historical monuments in India, Hawa Mahal stands testimony to the rich Rajputana architecture.</string>
    <string name="Aksardhamtempleinfo">"Akshardham" means the divine abode of God. It is hailed as an eternal place of devotion, purity and peace. Swaminarayan Akshardham at New Delhi is a Mandir – an abode of God, a Hindu house of worship, and a spiritual and cultural campus dedicated to devotion, learning and harmony. Timeless Hindu spiritual messages, vibrant devotional traditions and ancient architecture all are echoed in its art and architecture.</string>
</resources>